Third	O
was	O
Ford	B-ORG
with	O
35,563	O
registrations	O
,	O
or	O
11.7	O
percent	O
.	O

4.	O
Mika	B-PER
Hakkinen	I-PER
(	O
Finland	B-LOC
)	O
McLaren	B-ORG
1:54.754	O

Ford	B-ORG
owns	O
138.643	O
million	O
shares	O
in	O
the	O
firm	O
.	O

4.	O
Mika	B-PER
Hakkinen	I-PER
(	O
Finland	B-LOC
)	O
McLaren	B-ORG
1:54.754	O

Salim	B-PER
Malik	I-PER
not	O
out	O
2	O

Belmondo	B-PER
(	O
France	B-LOC
)	O
Ennea	B-MISC
Ferrari	I-MISC
F40	I-MISC
167	O

3.	O
John	B-PER
Regis	I-PER
(	O
Britain	B-LOC
)	O
20.63	O

3.	O
Jarmo	B-PER
Kytolehto	I-PER
(	O
Finland	B-LOC
)	O
Ford	B-MISC
Escort	I-MISC
2:37	O

LONDON	B-LOC
1996-08-22	O

4.	O
Mika	B-PER
Hakkinen	I-PER
(	O
Finland	B-LOC
)	O
McLaren	B-ORG
1:54.754	O

Belmondo	B-PER
(	O
France	B-LOC
)	O
Ennea	B-MISC
Ferrari	I-MISC
F40	I-MISC
167	O

AMSTERDAM	B-LOC
1996-08-25	O

BERLIN	B-LOC
1996-08-28	O

--	O
Bangkok	B-LOC
newsroom	O
662-252-9950	O

Third	O
was	O
Ford	B-ORG
with	O
35,563	O
registrations	O
,	O
or	O
11.7	O
percent	O
.	O

PRESS	O
DIGEST	O
-	O
Iraq	B-LOC
-	O
Aug	O
22	O
.	O

PHOENIX	B-LOC
1996-08-22	O

Total	O
Assets	O
14,196	O
7,138	O

Distances	O
:	O
a	O
short	O
head	O
,	O
1-1/4	O
lengths	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-	O

Mypa-47	B-ORG
win	O
2-1	O
on	O
aggregate	O
.	O

7.	O
Ireland	B-LOC
8.45	O

The	O
rates	O
are	O
:	O

3.	O
John	B-PER
Regis	I-PER
(	O
Britain	B-LOC
)	O
20.63	O

3.	O
Michael	B-PER
Schumacher	I-PER
(	O
Germany	B-LOC
)	O
39	O

52	O
seconds	O

BALTIMORE	B-LOC
1996-08-25	O

Lillestrom	B-ORG
19	O
9	O
5	O
5	O
38	O
29	O
32	O

201	O
Stephen	B-PER
Ames	I-PER
(	O
Trinidad	B-LOC
)	O
68	O
65	O
68	O
,	O
Roger	B-PER
Chapman	I-PER
72	O
62	O
67	O
,	O

Vitesse	B-ORG
Arnhem	I-ORG
1	O
(	O
Van	B-PER
Wanrooy	I-PER
58th	O
)	O
Utrecht	B-ORG
0	O
.	O

AMSTERDAM	B-LOC
1996-08-25	O

Sparta	B-ORG
Rotterdam	I-ORG
2	O
0	O
1	O
1	O
0	O
1	O
1	O

AZ	B-ORG
Alkmaar	I-ORG
2	O
0	O
1	O
1	O
0	O
2	O
1	O

-DOCSTART-	O

CALL	O
:	O
Non-Callable	O
NIC	O

PARIS	B-LOC
1996-08-26	O

TUNIS	B-LOC
1996-08-26	O

roughly	O
3	O
percent	O
.	O
"	O

CYCLING	O
-	O
WORLD	O
CHAMPIONSHIP	O
RESULTS	O
.	O

A.	B-PER
Stewart	I-PER
lbw	O
b	O
Waqar	B-PER
Younis	I-PER
48	O

M.	B-PER
Maynard	I-PER
b	O
Wasim	B-PER
Akram	I-PER
41	O

W	O
D	O
L	O
G	O
/	O
F	O
G	O
/	O
A	O
P	O

Shr	O
(	O
baht	O
)	O
8.32	O
vs	O
6.66	O

--	O
Bangkok	B-LOC
newsroom	O
662-252-9950	O

The	O
CEO	B-PER
of	O
Apple	B-ORG
announced	O
a	O
new	O
line	O
of	O
products	O
at	O
their	O
headquarters	O
in	O
Cupertino	B-LOC
yesterday.	O

The	O
famous	O
author	O
J.K.	B-PER
Rowling	I-PER
is	O
releasing	O
a	O
new	O
book	B-MISC
in	O
the	O
Harry	B-ORG
Potter	I-ORG
series	O
next	O
month.	O

NASA	B-ORG
is	O
launching	O
a	O
new	O
mission	B-MISC
to	O
explore	O
the	O
moons	O
of	O
Jupiter	B-LOC
next	O
year.	O

The	O
popular	O
fast-food	O
chain	O
McDonald's	B-ORG
is	O
introducing	O
a	O
new	O
vegetarian	B-MISC
burger	I-MISC
to	O
their	O
menu.	O

The	O
renowned	O
actor	O
Denzel	B-PER
Washington	I-PER
won	O
the	O
Best	O
Actor	O
award	B-MISC
at	O
the	O
Oscars	B-LOC
last	O
night.	O

The	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
and	O
China	B-LOC
are	O
negotiating	O
a	O
new	O
trade	B-MISC
agreement	I-MISC
to	O
address	O
ongoing	O
tariffs.	O

The	O
popular	O
social	O
media	O
platform	O
Facebook	B-ORG
is	O
facing	O
criticism	O
over	O
its	O
privacy	B-MISC
policies.	O

The	O
renowned	O
artist	O
Banksy	B-PER
has	O
donated	O
a	O
new	O
piece	O
of	O
artwork	O
to	O
a	O
museum	B-LOC
in	O
London.	O

The	O
famous	O
athlete	O
Simone	B-PER
Biles	I-PER
withdrew	O
from	O
the	O
Olympics	B-LOC
citing	O
mental	B-MISC
health	I-MISC
concerns.	O

The	O
technology	O
giant	O
Google	B-ORG
is	O
investing	O
$1	O
billion	O
in	O
a	O
new	O
data	B-MISC
center	I-MISC
in	O
Texas.	O

The	O
renowned	O
musician	O
Beyonce	B-PER
is	O
set	O
to	O
headline	O
the	O
Coachella	B-LOC
music	B-MISC
festival	I-MISC
next	O
year.	O

The	O
European	B-ORG
Union	I-ORG
is	O
imposing	O
new	O
sanctions	B-MISC
on	O
Russia	B-LOC
over	O
their	O
involvement	O
in	O
the	O
Ukraine	B-LOC
conflict.	O

The	O
popular	O
clothing	O
retailer	O
H&M	B-ORG
is	O
facing	O
backlash	O
over	O
accusations	O
of	O
forced	B-MISC
labor	I-MISC
in	O
their	O
supply	O
chain.	O

The	O
renowned	O
chef	O
Gordon	B-PER
Ramsay	I-PER
is	O
opening	B-MISC
a	O
new	O
restaurant	B-MISC
in	O
Paris	B-LOC
next	O
month.	O

The	O
United	B-LOC
Nations	I-LOC
has	O
launched	O
a	O
new	O
initiative	B-MISC
to	O
combat	O
climate	B-MISC
change	I-MISC
and	O
promote	O
sustainable	O
development.	O

The	O
popular	O
ride-sharing	O
company	O
Uber	B-ORG
is	O
facing	O
a	O
lawsuit	B-MISC
over	O
the	O
classification	O
of	O
their	O
drivers	O
as	O
independent	O
contractors.	O

The	O
renowned	O
author	O
Toni	B-PER
Morrison	I-PER
posthumously	O
receives	O
a	O
Presidential	B-MISC
Medal	I-MISC
of	I-MISC
Freedom	I-MISC
from	O
President	B-PER
Obama.	O

The	O
World	B-ORG
Economic	I-ORG
Forum	I-ORG
has	O
named	O
climate	O
change	O
as	O
the	O
top	O
global	B-MISC
risk	I-MISC
in	O
their	O
annual	O
report.	O

The	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
Congress	B-ORG
has	O
passed	O
a	O
new	O
infrastructure	B-MISC
bill,	O
providing	O
funding	O
for	O
roads,	O
bridges,	O
and	O
broadband.	O

The	O
famous	O
singer	O
Adele	B-PER
is	O
releasing	O
a	O
new	O
album	B-MISC
next	O
month,	O
her	O
first	O
in	O
six	O
years.	O

The	O
tech	O
company	O
Apple	B-ORG
is	O
set	O
to	O
release	B-MISC
a	O
new	O
iPhone	B-MISC
with	O
5G	O
capabilities	O
later	O
this	O
year.	O

The	O
famous	O
basketball	B-LOC
player	O
Kobe	B-PER
Bryant	I-PER
is	O
posthumously	O
inducted	O
into	O
the	O
Basketball	O
Hall	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Fame.	O

The	O
United	B-ORG
Nations	I-ORG
refugee	I-ORG
agency	I-ORG
reports	O
a	O
surge	O
in	O
displacement	B-MISC
due	O
to	O
conflict	O
and	O
persecution	O
worldwide.	O

The	O
popular	O
streaming	O
platform	O
Netflix	B-ORG
is	O
facing	O
criticism	O
over	O
the	O
release	O
of	O
a	O
controversial	B-MISC
new	O
show.	O

The	O
European	B-ORG
Central	I-ORG
Bank	I-ORG
has	O
announced	O
plans	O
to	O
roll	O
out	O
a	O
digital	B-MISC
euro	I-MISC
in	O
the	O
coming	O
years.	O

The	O
famous	O
singer	O
Taylor	B-PER
Swift	I-PER
is	O
re-recording	O
her	O
old	O
albums	O
in	O
a	O
dispute	O
over	O
music	B-MISC
ownership.	O

The	O
World	B-ORG
Health	I-ORG
Organization	I-ORG
has	O
approved	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
a	O
new	O
vaccine	B-MISC
for	O
malaria	B-MISC
in	O
African	O
countries.	O

The	O
popular	O
social	O
media	O
platform	O
TikTok	B-ORG
is	O
facing	O
scrutiny	O
over	O
data	B-MISC
privacy	I-MISC
concerns.	O

The	O
United	B-ORG
Nations	I-ORG
Climate	B-MISC
Change	I-MISC
Conference	I-MISC
will	O
be	O
held	O
in	O
Glasgow,	B-LOC
Scotland	I-LOC
later	O
this	O
year.	O

The	O
famous	O
actor	O
Tom	B-PER
Hanks	I-PER
has	O
been	O
cast	O
to	O
play	O
Geppetto	O
in	O
Disney's	O
live-action	O
Pinocchio	B-MISC
movie.	O

The	O
tech	O
giant	O
Microsoft	B-ORG
is	O
acquiring	O
the	O
voice	O
technology	O
company	O
Nuance	B-ORG
Communications	I-ORG
for	O
$19.7	O
billion.	O

The	O
renowned	O
economist	O
Joseph	B-PER
Stiglitz	I-PER
has	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
global	B-MISC
wealth	I-MISC
tax	I-MISC
to	O
address	O
income	O
inequality.	O

The	O
popular	O
fast-food	O
chain	O
McDonald's	B-ORG
is	O
testing	O
a	O
new	O
plant-based	B-MISC
burger	I-MISC
in	O
select	O
locations.	O

The	O
famous	O
musician	O
Prince	B-PER
is	O
posthumously	O
releasing	O
a	O
new	O
album	B-MISC
with	O
previously	O
unreleased	O
songs.	O

The	O
European	B-ORG
Union	I-ORG
is	O
launching	O
a	O
new	O
initiative	B-MISC
to	O
improve	O
digital	B-MISC
literacy	I-MISC
and	O
skills	O
for	O
citizens.	O

The	O
popular	O
video	O
conferencing	O
platform	O
Zoom	B-ORG
has	O
announced	O
plans	O
for	O
a	O
hybrid	B-MISC
work	I-MISC
model.	O

The	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
Supreme	B-ORG
Court	I-ORG
has	O
agreed	O
to	O
hear	O
a	O
case	B-MISC
challenging	O
abortion	B-MISC
rights.	O

The	O
famous	O
tennis	O
player	O
Naomi	B-PER
Osaka	I-PER
has	O
withdrawn	O
from	O
the	O
French	B-LOC
Open	I-LOC
to	O
prioritize	O
her	O
mental	B-MISC
health.	O

The	O
World	B-ORG
Economic	I-ORG
Forum	I-ORG
is	O
hosting	O
a	O
virtual	B-LOC
summit	B-MISC
on	O
sustainable	B-MISC
development	I-MISC
next	O
week.	O

The	O
famous	O
actress	O
Emma	B-PER
Stone	I-PER
has	O
given	O
birth	B-MISC
to	O
her	O
first	O
child	O
with	O
her	O
husband	O
Dave	B-PER
McCary.	O

The	O
tech	O
company	O
Amazon	B-ORG
is	O
facing	O
scrutiny	O
over	O
working	B-MISC
conditions	I-MISC
and	O
unionization	B-MISC
efforts	O
at	O
its	O
warehouses.	O

The	O
United	B-ORG
Nations	I-ORG
has	O
launched	O
an	O
appeal	B-MISC
for	O
humanitarian	B-MISC
aid	I-MISC
to	O
help	O
people	O
affected	O
by	O
conflict	O
and	O
natural	O
disasters	O
in	O
Yemen.	O

The	O
popular	O
ride-hailing	O
company	O
Uber	B-ORG
is	O
facing	O
a	O
lawsuit	B-MISC
over	O
alleged	O
discrimination	B-MISC
against	O
riders	O
with	O
disabilities.	O

The	O
famous	O
athlete	O
Simone	B-PER
Biles	I-PER
has	O
made	O
history	O
by	O
performing	O
a	O
Yurchenko	O
double	O
pike	O
vault	O
at	O
a	O
competition.	O

The	O
European	B-ORG
Union	I-ORG
has	O
approved	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
a	O
new	O
COVID-19	B-MISC
vaccine	I-MISC
from	O
Moderna	B-ORG
for	O
children	O
aged	O
12	O
to	O
17.	O

The	O
famous	O
musician	O
Kanye	B-PER
West	I-PER
is	O
reportedly	O
dating	B-MISC
model	O
Irina	B-PER
Shayk	I-PER
after	O
his	O
divorce	O
from	O
Kim	B-PER
Kardashian.	O

The	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
has	O
imposed	O
new	O
sanctions	B-MISC
on	O
Russia	B-LOC
over	O
cyberattacks	O
and	O
election	O
interference.	O

The	O
popular	O
social	O
media	O
platform	O
Instagram	B-ORG
is	O
launching	O
a	O
new	O
feature	B-MISC
to	O
allow	O
users	O
to	O
hide	O
like	B-MISC
counts	O
on	O
their	O
posts.	O

The	O
French	O
fashion	B-MISC
house	O
Chanel	B-ORG
has	O
announced	O
its	O
latest	O
collection	B-MISC
will	O
be	O
shown	O
in-person	O
during	O
Paris	B-MISC
Fashion	O
Week.	O

The	O
American	O
athlete	O
Sha'Carri	B-PER
Richardson	I-PER
has	O
been	O
banned	O
from	O
the	O
Tokyo	B-LOC
Olympics	B-ORG
after	O
testing	B-MISC
positive	O
for	O
marijuana.	O

The	O
social	O
media	O
giant	O
Facebook	B-ORG
is	O
facing	O
criticism	O
over	O
its	O
handling	O
of	O
misinformation	B-MISC
and	O
hate	B-MISC
speech	I-MISC
on	O
its	O
platform.	O

The	O
Hollywood	O
actress	O
Angelina	B-PER
Jolie	I-PER
has	O
donated	O
$1	O
million	O
to	O
help	O
fight	O
child	B-MISC
hunger	I-MISC
in	O
Ethiopia.	O

The	O
United	B-ORG
Nations	I-ORG
has	O
called	O
for	O
an	O
investigation	B-MISC
into	O
possible	O
war	B-MISC
crimes	I-MISC
committed	O
during	O
the	O
recent	O
conflict	O
between	O
Israel	O
and	O
Hamas	B-ORG
in	O
Gaza.	O

The	O
tech	O
giant	O
Apple	B-ORG
has	O
released	O
a	O
new	O
software	B-MISC
update	I-MISC
to	O
address	O
a	O
security	B-MISC
vulnerability	I-MISC
in	O
its	O
devices.	O

The	O
British	B-ORG
royal	B-MISC
family	I-MISC
has	O
announced	O
that	O
Prince	B-PER
Harry	I-PER
and	O
his	O
wife	O
Meghan	B-PER
Markle	I-PER
will	O
not	O
return	O
as	O
working	B-MISC
members	I-MISC
of	O
the	O
royal	O
family.	O

The	O
Indian	O
government	O
has	O
announced	O
a	O
new	O
vaccination	B-MISC
drive	I-MISC
to	O
vaccinate	O
all	O
adults	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
against	O
COVID-19.	O

The	O
American	O
retailer	O
Walmart	B-ORG
is	O
facing	O
a	O
boycott	B-MISC
over	O
its	O
decision	O
to	O
stop	O
selling	O
certain	O
firearms	B-MISC
and	O
ammunition.	O

The	O
Canadian	O
singer	O
Justin	B-PER
Bieber	I-PER
has	O
announced	O
a	O
new	O
album	B-MISC
and	O
tour	B-MISC
for	O
later	O
this	O
year.	O

The	O
World	B-ORG
Health	I-ORG
Organization	I-ORG
has	O
declared	O
a	O
global	B-MISC
emergency	I-MISC
over	O
the	O
outbreak	O
of	O
a	O
new	O
strain	O
of	O
the	O
coronavirus.	O

The	O
American	O
billionaire	O
Elon	B-PER
Musk	I-PER
has	O
announced	O
plans	O
to	O
build	O
a	O
new	B-MISC
city	I-MISC
on	O
Mars	B-LOC
by	O
2050.	O

The	O
British	O
Prime	O
Minister	O
Boris	B-PER
Johnson	I-PER
has	O
announced	O
a	O
new	O
plan	O
to	O
tackle	O
climate	B-MISC
change	I-MISC
by	O
reducing	O
the	O
country's	O
carbon	B-MISC
emissions.	O

The	O
tech	O
giant	O
Amazon	B-ORG
has	O
been	O
accused	O
of	O
unfairly	O
using	O
data	B-MISC
from	O
third-party	B-MISC
sellers	I-MISC
to	O
gain	O
an	O
unfair	O
advantage	O
in	O
its	O
own	O
retail	O
business.	O

The	O
Chinese	O
government	O
has	O
unveiled	O
a	O
new	O
five-year	B-MISC
plan	I-MISC
aimed	O
at	O
achieving	O
self-sufficiency	B-MISC
in	O
key	O
technologies	O
and	O
reducing	O
reliance	O
on	O
foreign	O
imports.	O

The	O
American	O
football	B-MISC
player	O
Tom	B-PER
Brady	I-PER
has	O
won	O
his	O
seventh	O
Super	B-MISC
Bowl	I-MISC
title,	O
leading	O
the	O
Tampa	B-ORG
Bay	I-ORG
Buccaneers	I-ORG
to	O
victory.	O

The	O
United	B-ORG
Nations	I-ORG
has	O
warned	O
of	O
a	O
looming	O
famine	B-MISC
in	O
Yemen,	O
where	O
millions	O
of	O
people	O
are	O
facing	O
food	B-MISC
insecurity	I-MISC
due	O
to	O
ongoing	O
conflict	O
and	O
economic	O
crisis.	O

The	O
American	O
pharmaceutical	O
company	O
Pfizer	B-ORG
has	O
announced	O
promising	O
results	O
from	O
its	O
COVID-19	B-MISC
vaccine	I-MISC
trial,	O
showing	O
95%	O
efficacy	O
against	O
the	O
virus.	O

The	O
Australian	O
government	B-MISC
has	O
apologized	O
to	O
victims	O
of	O
institutional	O
child	B-MISC
abuse,	I-MISC
following	O
a	O
five-year	O
inquiry	O
that	O
exposed	O
widespread	O
abuse	O
in	O
schools,	O
churches,	O
and	O
other	O
organizations.	O

The	O
American	O
rapper	O
Kanye	B-PER
West	I-PER
has	O
filed	O
for	O
divorce	B-MISC
from	O
his	O
wife	O
Kim	B-PER
Kardashian,	O
ending	B-MISC
their	O
six-year	O
marriage.	O

The	O
European	B-LOC
Union	I-LOC
has	O
approved	O
a	O
new	O
climate	B-MISC
law	I-MISC
that	O
commits	O
the	O
bloc	O
to	O
reach	O
carbon	B-MISC
neutrality	I-MISC
by	O
2050.	O

The	O
American	O
actress	O
and	O
singer	O
Jennifer	B-PER
Lopez	I-PER
has	O
been	O
named	O
as	O
the	O
new	O
face	O
of	O
a	O
luxury	B-ORG
fashion	B-MISC
brand.	O

The	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
and	O
China	B-LOC
have	O
agreed	O
to	O
cooperate	O
on	O
climate	B-MISC
change,	I-MISC
despite	O
ongoing	O
tensions	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
countries	O
on	O
other	O
issues.	O

The	O
International	B-ORG
Olympic	I-ORG
Committee	I-ORG
has	O
announced	O
that	O
the	O
2024	O
Summer	B-MISC
Olympics	I-MISC
will	O
be	O
held	O
in	O
Paris,	B-LOC
France.	O

The	O
American	O
tech	O
company	O
Apple	B-ORG
has	O
announced	O
plans	O
to	O
invest	O
$1	O
billion	O
in	O
a	O
new	O
campus	O
in	O
North	B-LOC
Carolina,	I-LOC
creating	O
thousands	O
of	O
jobs	O
in	O
the	O
state.	O

The	O
World	B-ORG
Trade	I-ORG
Organization	I-ORG
has	O
appointed	O
its	O
first	B-MISC
female	I-MISC
and	O
first	O
African	B-MISC
Director-General,	O
Ngozi	B-PER
Okonjo-Iweala	I-PER
from	O
Nigeria.	O

The	O
Indian	O
government	B-MISC
has	O
imposed	O
new	O
restrictions	O
on	O
social	B-MISC
media	I-MISC
platforms	O
in	O
the	O
country,	O
including	O
Facebook,	O
Twitter,	O
and	O
WhatsApp.	O

The	O
American	O
fashion	B-MISC
designer	O
Kate	B-PER
Spade	I-PER
has	O
launched	O
a	O
new	O
collection	B-MISC
inspired	O
by	O
the	O
colors	O
and	O
patterns	O
of	O
the	O
Italian	B-MISC
coast.	O

The	O
United	B-ORG
Nations	I-ORG
has	O
warned	O
that	O
the	O
world	O
is	O
facing	O
a	O
"catastrophic	O
moral	O
failure"	O
over	O
the	O
unequal	O
distribution	O
of	O
COVID-19	B-MISC
vaccines,	I-MISC
with	O
wealthy	O
countries	O
receiving	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
doses.	O

The	B-MISC
American	O
singer	O
and	O
songwriter	O
Taylor	B-PER
Swift	I-PER
has	O
won	O
Album	B-MISC
of	I-MISC
the	O
Year	B-MISC
at	O
the	O
Grammy	B-ORG
Awards	I-ORG
for	O
the	O
third	O
time	O
in	O
her	O
career.	O

The	O
United	B-ORG
Nations	I-ORG
has	O
condemned	O
the	O
military	B-MISC
coup	I-MISC
in	O
Myanmar	B-LOC
and	O
called	O
for	O
the	O
release	O
of	O
Aung	B-PER
San	I-PER
Suu	I-PER
Kyi	I-PER
and	O
other	O
political	B-MISC
prisoners.	O

The	O
American	O
social	B-MISC
media	I-MISC
platform	O
Twitter	B-ORG
has	O
permanently	O
suspended	O
the	O
account	B-MISC
of	O
former	O
US	O
President	O
Donald	B-PER
Trump.	O

The	O
European	B-ORG
Space	B-MISC
Agency	B-ORG
has	O
successfully	O
landed	O
a	O
spacecraft	O
on	O
an	O
asteroid	B-MISC
for	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
in	O
history.	O

The	O
French	O
luxury	B-MISC
goods	I-MISC
conglomerate	O
LVMH	B-ORG
has	O
acquired	O
the	O
American	O
jewelry	O
company	O
Tiffany	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Co.	I-ORG
for	O
$16.2	O
billion.	O

The	O
British	O
Prime	O
Minister	O
Boris	B-PER
Johnson	I-PER
has	O
announced	O
a	O
new	O
national	O
lockdown	B-MISC
in	O
response	O
to	O
a	O
surge	O
in	O
COVID-19	B-MISC
cases.	O

The	O
United	B-ORG
States	I-ORG
has	O
imposed	O
new	O
sanctions	B-MISC
on	O
Russia	B-LOC
in	O
response	O
to	O
the	O
poisoning	O
of	O
opposition	B-MISC
leader	O
Alexei	B-PER
Navalny.	O

The	O
American	O
streaming	B-MISC
service	O
Netflix	B-ORG
has	O
announced	O
plans	O
to	O
invest	O
$500	O
million	O
in	O
original	O
content	O
production	O
in	O
South	B-LOC
Korea.	O

The	O
World	B-ORG
Health	I-ORG
Organization	I-ORG
has	O
approved	O
the	O
use	B-MISC
of	O
the	O
Johnson	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Johnson	O
COVID-19	B-MISC
vaccine	I-MISC
for	O
emergency	B-MISC
use.	O

The	O
American	O
fashion	O
retailer	O
Gap	B-ORG
has	O
announced	O
plans	O
to	O
close	O
all	O
of	O
its	O
stores	O
in	O
the	O
United	B-LOC
Kingdom	I-LOC
and	O
Ireland.	O

The	O
Chinese	B-ORG
government	I-ORG
has	O
announced	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
allow	O
couples	O
to	O
have	O
up	O
to	O
three	O
children,	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
previous	O
limit	O
of	O
two.	O

The	O
American	O
pharmaceutical	O
company	O
Pfizer	B-ORG
has	O
announced	O
that	O
its	O
COVID-19	B-MISC
vaccine	I-MISC
is	O
100%	O
effective	O
in	O
children	O
aged	O
12	O
to	O
15.	O

The	O
Italian	O
fashion	B-MISC
brand	O
Versace	B-ORG
has	O
launched	O
a	O
collection	B-MISC
of	O
clothing	B-MISC
made	O
from	O
sustainable	B-MISC
materials.	O

The	O
American	O
professional	O
basketball	O
player	O
LeBron	B-PER
James	I-PER
has	O
become	O
a	O
minority	O
owner	O
of	O
the	O
Boston	B-ORG
Red	I-ORG
Sox	I-ORG
baseball	O
team.	O

The	O
Australian	B-ORG
government	I-ORG
has	O
announced	O
a	O
$600	O
million	O
package	O
to	O
support	O
the	O
country's	O
struggling	O
tourism	B-MISC
industry.	O

The	O
American	O
multinational	O
investment	B-MISC
bank	O
Goldman	B-ORG
Sachs	I-ORG
has	O
pledged	O
to	O
invest	O
$10	O
billion	O
in	O
initiatives	O
to	O
promote	O
economic	O
opportunity	O
for	O
black	O
women.	O

The	O
French	O
President	O
Emmanuel	B-PER
Macron	I-PER
has	O
unveiled	O
a	O
plan	O
to	O
gradually	O
reopen	O
the	O
country's	O
cultural	B-MISC
and	O
sporting	O
venues	B-MISC
after	O
months	O
of	O
closure	O
due	O
to	O
the	O
COVID-19	B-MISC
pandemic.	O

The	O
American	O
e-commerce	O
giant	O
Amazon	B-ORG
has	O
announced	O
plans	O
to	O
acquire	O
the	O
Hollywood	B-LOC
studio	O
MGM	B-ORG
for	O
$8.45	O
billion.	O

The	O
Japanese	O
tennis	O
player	O
Naomi	B-PER
Osaka	I-PER
has	O
withdrawn	O
from	O
the	O
French	B-ORG
Open	I-ORG
citing	O
mental	B-MISC
health	I-MISC
concerns.	O

The	O
Canadian	B-ORG
government	I-ORG
has	O
pledged	O
to	O
build	O
35,000	O
new	O
affordable	O
housing	B-MISC
units	O
over	O
the	O
next	O
10	O
years.	O

The	O
United	B-ORG
Nations	I-ORG
has	O
warned	O
of	O
a	O
worsening	O
humanitarian	B-MISC
crisis	I-MISC
in	O
Yemen,	O
as	O
fighting	O
between	O
government	O
forces	O
and	O
Houthi	O
rebels	O
intensifies.	O

The	O
British	O
actor	O
Tom	B-PER
Hiddleston	I-PER
has	O
been	O
cast	O
as	O
the	O
lead	O
in	O
the	O
upcoming	O
TV	B-MISC
adaptation	I-MISC
of	O
the	O
novel	O
"The	O
Essex	O
Serpent."	O

The	O
American	O
musician	O
Beyoncé	B-PER
has	O
released	O
a	O
new	O
album,	O
"Black	O
is	O
King,"	O
which	O
celebrates	O
African	O
culture	O
and	O
history.	O

The	O
Indian	B-ORG
government	I-ORG
has	O
approved	O
a	O
$1.8	O
billion	O
plan	O
to	O
provide	O
free	O
food	B-MISC
grains	O
to	O
800	O
million	O
people	O
amid	O
the	O
COVID-19	B-MISC
pandemic.	O

The	O
American	O
multinational	O
technology	B-MISC
company	O
Google	B-ORG
has	O
announced	O
plans	O
to	O
invest	O
$7	O
billion	O
in	O
data	O
centers	O
and	O
office	O
space	O
across	O
the	O
United	B-LOC
States.	O

The	O
Brazilian	O
football	O
player	O
Neymar	B-PER
Jr.	I-PER
has	O
signed	O
a	O
contract	B-MISC
extension	I-MISC
with	O
Paris	B-ORG
Saint-Germain,	O
keeping	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
team	O
until	O
2025.	O

The	O
Japanese	O
car	O
manufacturer	O
Toyota	B-ORG
has	O
announced	O
plans	O
to	O
develop	O
a	O
hydrogen-powered	O
engine	O
for	O
heavy-duty	O
trucks	O
in	O
collaboration	O
with	O
its	O
subsidiary	O
Hino	B-ORG
Motors.	O

The	O
Australian	B-ORG
government	I-ORG
has	O
committed	O
to	O
spending	O
$2.3	O
billion	O
to	O
improve	O
mental	B-MISC
health	I-MISC
services	O
in	O
the	O
country,	O
including	O
the	O
establishment	O
of	O
new	O
treatment	O
centers.	O

The	O
American	O
retail	O
giant	O
Walmart	B-ORG
has	O
announced	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
invest	O
$350	O
billion	O
in	O
US-made	O
products	O
over	O
the	O
next	O
10	O
years.	O

The	O
American	O
technology	B-MISC
company	O
Amazon	B-ORG
has	O
announced	O
plans	O
to	O
hire	O
75,000	O
new	O
employees	O
in	O
the	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
and	O
Canada.	O

The	O
Argentine	O
football	O
legend	O
Diego	B-PER
Maradona	I-PER
has	O
passed	O
away	O
at	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
60	O
due	O
to	O
a	O
heart	O
attack.	O

The	O
United	B-ORG
States	I-ORG
has	O
announced	O
plans	O
to	O
donate	O
500	O
million	O
doses	O
of	O
the	O
Pfizer-BioNTech	O
COVID-19	B-MISC
vaccine	I-MISC
to	O
low-income	O
countries.	O

The	O
British	B-ORG
royal	B-MISC
family	I-MISC
has	O
announced	O
the	O
birth	B-MISC
of	O
a	O
daughter	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
and	O
Duchess	O
of	O
Sussex,	O
Prince	B-PER
Harry	I-PER
and	O
Meghan	B-PER
Markle.	O

The	O
Australian	B-ORG
Open	I-ORG
tennis	O
tournament	O
has	O
been	O
postponed	O
by	O
three	O
weeks	O
due	O
to	O
COVID-19	B-MISC
quarantine	O
restrictions.	O

The	O
American	O
social	O
media	O
company	O
Facebook	B-ORG
has	O
announced	O
plans	O
to	O
launch	O
a	O
smartwatch	O
that	O
can	O
connect	O
to	O
other	O
fitness	O
devices	O
and	O
display	O
social	O
media	O
notifications.	O

The	O
Mexican	B-ORG
government	I-ORG
has	O
announced	O
plans	O
to	O
invest	O
$1.6	O
billion	O
to	O
upgrade	O
the	O
country's	O
railway	O
network,	O
including	O
the	O
construction	O
of	O
a	O
new	O
train	O
line	O
in	O
the	O
Yucatan	O
Peninsula.	O

The	O
American	O
streaming	O
service	O
Netflix	B-ORG
has	O
announced	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
produce	O
a	O
new	O
television	O
series	O
based	O
on	O
the	O
popular	O
video	B-MISC
game	O
"Assassin's	O
Creed."	O

The	O
Chinese	O
e-commerce	O
giant	O
Alibaba	B-ORG
has	O
been	O
fined	O
a	O
record	O
$2.8	O
billion	O
by	O
Chinese	O
regulators	O
for	O
anti-competitive	O
practices.	O

The	B-ORG
United	I-ORG
Nations	I-ORG
has	O
announced	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
holding	O
a	O
summit	O
on	O
climate	B-MISC
change	I-MISC
in	O
New	B-LOC
York	I-LOC
next	O
month.	O

The	O
CEO	O
of	O
Amazon,	O
Jeff	B-PER
Bezos,	O
has	O
announced	O
his	O
resignation	O
from	O
the	O
company.	O

The	B-ORG
government	I-ORG
of	O
India	B-LOC
has	O
announced	O
a	O
nationwide	O
lockdown	O
in	O
response	O
to	O
the	O
surge	O
in	O
COVID-19	B-MISC
cases.	O

The	O
famous	O
actor	O
and	O
philanthropist,	O
George	B-PER
Clooney,	O
has	O
donated	O
$1	O
million	O
to	O
support	O
relief	O
efforts	O
in	O
Afghanistan.	O

The	B-ORG
World	I-ORG
Health	I-ORG
Organization	I-ORG
has	O
declared	O
the	O
Ebola	B-MISC
outbreak	I-MISC
in	O
Guinea	B-LOC
to	O
be	O
over.	O

The	B-ORG
European	I-ORG
Union	I-ORG
and	O
United	B-LOC
Kingdom	I-LOC
have	O
reached	O
a	O
historic	O
agreement	O
on	O
their	O
post-Brexit	O
relationship.	O

The	O
popular	O
ride-sharing	B-MISC
company,	O
Uber,	O
has	O
announced	O
its	O
plans	O
to	O
expand	O
its	O
services	O
to	O
100	O
new	O
cities.	O

The	O
American	O
astronaut,	O
Sally	B-PER
Ride,	O
has	O
been	O
posthumously	O
awarded	O
the	O
Presidential	B-MISC
Medal	I-MISC
of	I-MISC
Freedom.	O

The	B-ORG
renowned	O
art	B-MISC
museum,	O
The	O
Louvre,	O
has	O
unveiled	O
a	O
new	O
exhibit	B-MISC
featuring	O
works	O
by	O
Vincent	B-PER
van	I-PER
Gogh.	O

The	O
famous	O
fashion	B-MISC
designer,	O
Karl	B-PER
Lagerfeld,	O
has	O
passed	O
away	O
at	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
85.	O

The	B-ORG
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
government	O
has	O
imposed	O
sanctions	O
on	O
a	O
North	B-ORG
Korean	I-ORG
cybercrime	I-ORG
organization	I-ORG
accused	O
of	O
stealing	O
over	O
$1.3	O
billion	O
in	O
cryptocurrency.	O

The	O
famous	O
singer	O
and	O
actress,	O
Jennifer	B-PER
Lopez,	O
has	O
launched	O
a	O
new	O
line	O
of	O
skincare	B-MISC
products.	O

The	B-ORG
European	I-ORG
Central	I-ORG
Bank	I-ORG
has	O
announced	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
begin	O
a	O
review	O
of	O
its	O
monetary	B-MISC
policy	I-MISC
strategy.	O

The	B-ORG
Indian	I-ORG
government	I-ORG
has	O
unveiled	O
a	O
new	O
plan	O
to	O
provide	O
free	O
education	B-MISC
to	O
girls	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
18.	O

The	O
CEO	O
of	O
Tesla,	O
Elon	B-PER
Musk,	O
has	O
announced	O
plans	O
to	O
build	O
a	O
new	O
factory	B-MISC
in	O
Texas.	O

The	B-ORG
United	I-ORG
Nations	I-ORG
has	O
called	O
for	O
an	O
end	O
to	O
the	O
violence	B-MISC
in	O
Myanmar	B-LOC
following	O
the	O
military	B-MISC
coup.	O

The	O
popular	O
social	B-MISC
media	I-MISC
platform,	O
Instagram,	O
has	O
introduced	O
new	O
features	O
to	O
combat	O
online	B-MISC
harassment	I-MISC
and	O
hate	O
speech.	O

The	O
famous	O
author,	O
J.K.	B-PER
Rowling,	O
has	O
announced	O
that	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
releasing	O
a	O
new	O
children's	B-MISC
book	I-MISC
later	O
this	O
year.	O

The	B-ORG
Chinese	I-ORG
government	I-ORG
has	O
announced	O
plans	O
to	O
launch	O
a	O
new	O
space	B-MISC
station	I-MISC
by	O
2022.	O

The	O
famous	O
football	B-MISC
player,	O
Lionel	B-PER
Messi,	O
has	O
signed	O
a	O
new	O
contract	O
with	O
Paris	B-ORG
Saint-Germain.	O

The	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
government	O
has	O
reached	O
a	O
historic	O
agreement	O
with	O
Mexico	B-LOC
and	O
Canada	B-LOC
to	O
replace	O
NAFTA	B-MISC
with	O
a	O
new	O
trade	B-MISC
deal.	O

The	O
famous	O
singer	O
and	O
songwriter,	O
Taylor	B-PER
Swift,	O
has	O
announced	O
her	O
upcoming	O
tour	B-MISC
dates	O
in	O
support	O
of	O
her	O
new	O
album.	O

The	B-ORG
Indian	I-ORG
Space	I-ORG
Research	I-ORG
Organization	I-ORG
has	O
successfully	O
launched	O
a	O
record-breaking	B-MISC
143	O
satellites	O
into	O
orbit	O
on	O
a	O
single	O
rocket.	O

The	B-ORG
United	I-ORG
Nations	I-ORG
has	O
announced	O
a	O
new	O
plan	O
to	O
address	O
the	O
global	B-LOC
refugee	B-MISC
crisis	I-MISC
by	O
increasing	O
funding	B-MISC
and	O
resettlement	O
efforts.	O

The	O
famous	O
actor,	O
Tom	B-PER
Hanks,	O
has	O
been	O
cast	O
to	O
play	O
the	O
role	O
of	O
Geppetto	O
in	O
the	O
upcoming	O
live-action	O
adaptation	B-MISC
of	O
Pinocchio.	O

The	B-ORG
Chinese	I-ORG
government	I-ORG
has	O
announced	O
plans	O
to	O
launch	O
a	O
digital	B-MISC
version	O
of	O
its	O
national	O
currency,	B-MISC
the	O
yuan.	O

The	O
CEO	O
of	O
Facebook,	O
Mark	B-PER
Zuckerberg,	O
has	O
testified	O
before	O
Congress	O
on	O
issues	O
related	O
to	O
data	B-MISC
privacy	I-MISC
and	O
security.	O

The	B-ORG
Australian	I-ORG
government	I-ORG
has	O
unveiled	O
a	O
new	O
plan	O
to	O
invest	O
in	O
renewable	B-MISC
energy	I-MISC
and	O
reduce	O
carbon	B-MISC
emissions	I-MISC
by	O
2050.	O

The	O
famous	O
basketball	B-MISC
player,	O
LeBron	B-PER
James,	O
has	O
announced	O
his	O
decision	O
to	O
join	O
the	O
Los	B-ORG
Angeles	I-ORG
Lakers.	O

The	B-ORG
World	I-ORG
Health	B-MISC
Organization	B-ORG
has	O
declared	O
the	O
outbreak	O
of	O
the	O
Zika	B-MISC
virus	I-MISC
in	O
South	B-LOC
America	I-LOC
a	O
global	O
public	B-MISC
health	O
emergency.	O

The	O
European	B-LOC
Union	I-LOC
has	O
imposed	O
sanctions	B-MISC
on	O
Russia	B-LOC
over	O
the	O
poisoning	B-MISC
of	O
opposition	O
leader,	O
Alexei	B-PER
Navalny.	O

The	B-MISC
famous	O
actress,	O
Angelina	B-PER
Jolie,	O
has	O
been	O
named	O
as	O
the	O
Time	B-ORG
magazine's	O
Person	B-MISC
of	I-MISC
the	O
Year	B-MISC
for	O
her	O
humanitarian	B-MISC
work.	O

The	B-ORG
Japanese	I-ORG
government	I-ORG
has	O
declared	O
a	O
state	B-MISC
of	I-MISC
emergency	I-MISC
in	O
Tokyo	B-LOC
due	O
to	O
a	O
surge	O
in	O
COVID-19	B-MISC
cases.	O

The	O
popular	O
social	O
media	O
app,	O
TikTok,	O
has	O
been	O
banned	O
in	O
India	B-LOC
amid	O
concerns	O
over	O
data	B-MISC
privacy	I-MISC
and	O
security.	O

The	O
CEO	B-MISC
of	O
Amazon,	O
Jeff	B-PER
Bezos,	O
has	O
announced	O
his	O
plans	O
to	O
step	O
down	O
from	O
his	O
role	O
and	O
transition	O
to	O
the	O
position	O
of	O
executive	B-MISC
chairman.	O

The	B-ORG
United	I-ORG
Nations	I-ORG
Climate	B-MISC
Change	I-MISC
Conference,	I-MISC
COP26,	O
has	O
been	O
postponed	O
due	O
to	O
the	O
COVID-19	B-MISC
pandemic.	O

The	O
famous	O
author,	O
Stephen	B-PER
King,	O
has	O
announced	O
his	O
new	O
book,	O
Billy	B-MISC
Summers,	O
set	O
to	O
release	B-MISC
in	O
August	O
2021.	O

The	O
Chinese	O
government	O
has	O
launched	O
an	O
investigation	B-MISC
into	O
e-commerce	O
giant	O
Alibaba	B-ORG
over	O
alleged	O
monopolistic	B-MISC
practices.	O

The	O
famous	O
singer,	O
Adele,	O
has	O
announced	O
her	O
fourth	O
album	B-MISC
titled	O
"30"	B-MISC
to	O
be	O
released	O
on	O
November	O
19,	O
2021.	O

The	B-ORG
United	I-ORG
States	I-ORG
government	I-ORG
has	O
imposed	O
new	O
sanctions	B-MISC
on	O
Cuba	B-LOC
over	O
the	O
crackdown	O
on	O
anti-government	B-MISC
protesters.	O

The	O
famous	O
musician,	O
Prince,	O
has	O
passed	O
away	O
at	O
the	O
age	B-MISC
of	O
57.	O

The	B-ORG
US	I-ORG
government	I-ORG
has	O
reached	O
a	O
$1.9	B-MISC
trillion	I-MISC
COVID-19	I-MISC
relief	I-MISC
deal	O
after	O
months	O
of	O
negotiations.	O

The	O
iconic	O
Notre-Dame	B-MISC
cathedral	O
in	O
Paris	B-LOC
has	O
been	O
severely	O
damaged	O
by	O
a	O
fire.	O

The	O
tech	O
giant	O
Apple	B-ORG
has	O
announced	O
a	O
new	O
range	O
of	O
iPhone	B-MISC
models,	I-MISC
including	O
the	O
iPhone	O
13.	O

The	O
US	B-LOC
Capitol	B-MISC
has	O
been	O
stormed	O
by	O
supporters	O
of	O
outgoing	O
President	O
Donald	B-PER
Trump,	O
resulting	O
in	O
violent	O
clashes	O
with	O
police.	O

The	B-ORG
United	I-ORG
Nations	B-LOC
General	O
Assembly	O
has	O
adopted	O
a	O
resolution	B-MISC
calling	O
for	O
an	O
end	O
to	O
the	O
US	O
embargo	B-MISC
on	O
Cuba.	O

The	O
famous	O
tennis	B-MISC
player,	O
Naomi	B-PER
Osaka,	O
has	O
withdrawn	O
from	O
the	O
French	B-MISC
Open	I-MISC
citing	O
mental	B-MISC
health	I-MISC
concerns.	O

The	O
social	B-MISC
media	I-MISC
platform	O
Twitter	B-ORG
has	O
permanently	O
suspended	O
former	O
US	O
President	O
Donald	B-PER
Trump's	O
account.	O

The	B-ORG
Taliban	I-ORG
has	O
taken	O
control	B-MISC
of	O
Afghanistan's	O
capital,	O
Kabul,	B-LOC
following	O
the	O
withdrawal	B-MISC
of	O
US	B-ORG
and	O
NATO	B-ORG
forces.	O

The	O
CEO	O
of	O
Tesla,	O
Elon	B-PER
Musk,	O
has	O
become	O
the	O
world's	O
richest	O
person	O
with	O
a	O
net	B-MISC
worth	I-MISC
of	O
over	O
$200	O
billion.	O

The	O
UK	B-ORG
government	I-ORG
has	O
announced	O
plans	O
to	O
ban	B-MISC
the	O
sale	O
of	O
new	O
petrol	B-MISC
and	O
diesel	B-MISC
cars	I-MISC
from	O
2030	O
in	O
an	O
effort	O
to	O
reduce	O
carbon	B-MISC
emissions.	O

The	B-ORG
United	I-ORG
Nations	I-ORG
has	O
warned	O
of	O
a	O
famine	B-MISC
in	O
Yemen,	O
where	O
millions	O
of	O
people	O
are	O
facing	O
hunger	B-MISC
due	O
to	O
the	O
ongoing	O
conflict.	O

The	O
famous	O
actor,	O
Chadwick	B-PER
Boseman,	O
has	O
posthumously	O
won	O
a	O
Golden	B-ORG
Globe	I-ORG
award	B-MISC
for	O
his	O
role	O
in	O
"Ma	O
Rainey's	O
Black	O
Bottom".	O

The	O
European	B-LOC
Union	I-LOC
has	O
announced	O
a	O
plan	B-MISC
to	O
become	O
the	O
world's	O
first	O
carbon-neutral	B-MISC
continent	O
by	O
2050.	O

The	O
famous	O
fashion	O
designer,	O
Karl	B-PER
Lagerfeld,	O
has	O
passed	O
away	O
at	O
the	O
age	B-MISC
of	O
85.	O

The	O
US	O
government	O
has	O
launched	O
an	O
investigation	B-MISC
into	O
Facebook's	O
acquisition	B-MISC
of	O
Instagram	B-ORG
and	O
WhatsApp.	O

The	O
city	O
of	O
Venice,	B-LOC
Italy	I-LOC
is	O
experiencing	O
its	O
worst	O
flooding	B-MISC
in	O
over	O
50	O
years,	O
with	O
floodwaters	O
reaching	O
6	O
feet	O
above	O
sea	B-MISC
level.	O

The	O
International	B-ORG
Olympic	I-ORG
Committee	I-ORG
(IOC)	O
has	O
postponed	O
the	O
2020	O
Summer	O
Olympics	B-MISC
in	O
Tokyo	B-LOC
to	O
2021	O
due	O
to	O
the	O
COVID-19	O
pandemic.	O

The	O
famous	O
singer,	O
Taylor	B-PER
Swift,	O
has	O
re-recorded	O
her	O
album	B-MISC
"Fearless"	O
to	O
regain	O
control	B-MISC
of	O
her	O
music	B-MISC
catalog.	O

The	O
tech	O
giant	O
Apple	B-ORG
has	O
announced	O
a	O
new	O
lineup	O
of	O
products,	O
including	O
the	O
highly	O
anticipated	O
iPhone	B-MISC
13.	O

The	O
United	B-ORG
Nations	I-ORG
General	I-ORG
Assembly	I-ORG
has	O
called	O
for	O
an	O
immediate	O
end	O
to	O
the	O
violence	B-MISC
in	O
Myanmar	B-LOC
following	O
a	O
military	B-MISC
coup	I-MISC
earlier	O
this	O
year.	O

The	O
world's	O
largest	O
social	B-MISC
media	I-MISC
platform,	O
Facebook,	O
has	O
faced	O
criticism	O
over	O
its	O
handling	O
of	O
misinformation	B-MISC
during	O
the	O
COVID-19	B-MISC
pandemic.	O

The	O
famous	O
musician,	O
Prince,	O
has	O
been	O
posthumously	O
inducted	O
into	O
the	O
Rock	B-ORG
and	I-ORG
Roll	I-ORG
Hall	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Fame	I-ORG
for	O
his	O
contributions	O
to	O
music.	O

The	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
has	O
announced	O
a	O
plan	O
to	O
donate	O
500	O
million	O
COVID-19	B-MISC
vaccine	I-MISC
doses	O
to	O
other	O
countries	O
in	O
need.	O

The	O
European	O
football	O
governing	O
body,	O
UEFA,	O
has	O
announced	O
a	O
new	O
format	B-MISC
for	O
its	O
flagship	O
competition,	O
the	O
Champions	B-MISC
League,	O
starting	O
in	O
2024.	O

The	O
popular	O
video-sharing	O
app,	O
TikTok,	O
has	O
reached	O
over	O
3	O
billion	O
downloads	B-MISC
worldwide,	O
making	O
it	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
popular	O
apps	O
in	O
history.	O

The	O
state	O
of	O
California	B-LOC
in	O
the	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
is	O
experiencing	O
one	O
of	O
its	O
worst	O
droughts	O
in	O
history,	O
with	O
water	B-MISC
supplies	O
running	O
dangerously	O
low.	O

The	O
CEO	B-MISC
of	O
Amazon,	O
Jeff	B-PER
Bezos,	O
has	O
announced	O
his	O
plans	O
to	O
step	O
down	O
from	O
his	O
role	O
and	O
transition	B-MISC
to	O
the	O
position	O
of	O
executive	O
chairman.	O

The	O
world's	O
largest	O
annual	O
music	B-MISC
festival,	I-MISC
Coachella,	O
has	O
been	O
postponed	O
for	O
the	O
second	O
year	O
in	O
a	O
row	O
due	O
to	O
the	O
ongoing	O
COVID-19	B-MISC
pandemic.	O

The	O
American	O
actor	O
and	O
comedian,	O
Robin	B-PER
Williams,	O
has	O
been	O
posthumously	O
honored	O
with	O
a	O
lifetime	B-MISC
achievement	I-MISC
award	I-MISC
at	O
the	O
2022	O
Golden	B-ORG
Globe	I-ORG
Awards.	O

The	O
city	B-MISC
of	O
Tokyo	B-LOC
in	O
Japan	B-LOC
has	O
been	O
selected	O
to	O
host	B-MISC
the	O
2032	O
Summer	O
Olympics,	B-MISC
marking	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
the	O
city	O
will	O
host	O
the	O
games.	O

The	O
multinational	O
technology	B-MISC
company,	O
Microsoft,	B-ORG
has	O
announced	O
plans	O
to	O
acquire	O
the	O
video	B-MISC
game	O
company,	O
Activision	B-ORG
Blizzard,	O
in	O
a	O
deal	O
worth	O
$68.7	O
billion.	O

The	O
country	O
of	O
Haiti	B-LOC
has	O
been	O
hit	O
by	O
a	O
devastating	O
earthquake,	B-MISC
leaving	O
over	O
1,400	O
people	O
dead	O
and	O
many	O
more	O
injured	O
or	O
missing.	O

The	O
popular	O
coffee	O
chain,	O
Starbucks,	O
has	O
announced	O
plans	O
to	O
phase	O
out	O
single-use	O
plastic	B-MISC
straws	O
in	O
all	O
its	O
stores	O
worldwide.	O

The	O
British	B-ORG
royal	B-MISC
family	B-ORG
has	O
welcomed	O
a	O
new	O
addition	O
with	O
the	O
birth	B-MISC
of	O
Prince	B-PER
Harry	I-PER
and	O
Meghan	B-PER
Markle's	O
daughter,	O
Lilibet	B-PER
Diana.	O

The	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
and	O
Russia	B-LOC
have	O
agreed	O
to	O
extend	O
the	O
New	B-ORG
START	I-ORG
treaty,	O
a	O
nuclear	B-MISC
arms	I-MISC
control	I-MISC
agreement,	O
for	O
an	O
additional	O
five	O
years.	O

The	O
fashion	B-MISC
company,	O
Gucci,	O
has	O
announced	O
plans	O
to	O
become	O
a	O
carbon-neutral	O
brand	O
by	O
offsetting	O
its	O
greenhouse	O
gas	O
emissions	O
and	O
investing	O
in	O
renewable	O
energy.	O

The	O
country	O
of	O
Australia	B-LOC
has	O
been	O
experiencing	O
severe	O
wildfires,	B-MISC
with	O
over	O
100	O
blazes	O
burning	O
across	O
the	O
country's	O
eastern	O
coast.	O

The	O
social	B-MISC
media	I-MISC
platform,	O
Twitter,	O
has	O
permanently	O
suspended	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
former	O
U.S.	O
President	O
Donald	B-PER
Trump,	O
citing	O
concerns	O
about	O
the	O
incitement	O
of	O
violence.	O

The	O
World	B-ORG
Health	B-MISC
Organization	B-ORG
(WHO)	O
has	O
declared	O
the	O
outbreak	O
of	O
the	O
Omicron	B-MISC
variant	I-MISC
of	O
COVID-19	B-MISC
a	O
global	B-MISC
health	O
emergency,	O
urging	O
countries	O
to	O
take	O
swift	O
action	O
to	O
curb	O
its	O
spread.	O